api_key: 8u5ixtdnq9csc84cok0owswgo
spam_questions:
    - question: 'Is ice hot or cold?'
      answers: 'cold'
    - question: 'what color is an orange?'
      answers: 'orange'
    - question: 'what is two plus 3?'
      answers: '5,five'
    - question: 'what is 5 times two?'
      answers: '10,ten'
    - question: 'How many colors in the list, green, brown, foot and blue?'
      answers: '3,three'
    - question: 'what is Georges name?'
      answers: 'george'
    - question: '11 minus 1?'
      answers: '10,ten'
    - question: 'is boiling water hot or cold?'
      answers: 'hot'
    - question: 'what color is my blue shirt today?'
      answers: 'blue'
    - question: 'what is 16 plus 4?'
      answers: '20,twenty'